SUMMARY

Driven professional with broad technical skill set. Full Stack Developer with the ability to build web apps through the entire process. Hands on experience in two full stacks including MEAN and Python. Experienced in information gathering, development, testing and deployment.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering, University of Mumbai, Major - Chemical **Minor - Computer Science**, June 2013 **Coding Dojo** - Onsite Flex Bootcamp, San Jose December 2015

EXPERIENCE

Slice Technologies, San Mateo, California Software Engineer - Intern | Aug 2016 - Present

- Slice Watch Chrome Extension: A chrome extension which allows you to track product prices when you shop, and get email notifications whenever they drop. Featured on TechCrunch. Technologies: JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, HTML, CSS, Chrome Extension API. Demo
- Rest Services for Slice Watch: REST based backend service for Slice Watch chrome extension, supporting following features: Adds product to the list to be crawled, starts Cron job to crawl products, compute price drops, send email to users when price drops. *Technologies*: JavaScript, node.js, sequelize, AWS BeanStalk, AWS CloudWatch.
- UTM Impressions Tracking Services: Designed and developed a generic UTM impression tracking service for all Slice Client apps. Technologies: JavaScript, AWS Lambda, AWS API Gateway, AWS DynamoDB, AWS CloudWatch, CORS.
- Website for Slice Watch: Designed, developed and maintained the landing page for Slice Watch product. Implemented support for inline installation of chrome extension. *Technologies*: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap. Demo: <u>slice-watch.slice.com</u>
- Customer Services Tool: Performed bug-fixes for an internal Customer Service tool. *Technologies*: Java, JSP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL.

Coding Dojo, San Jose, California

Web Development - Student | Aug 2015 - Dec 2015

Intensive 14 week full-time web development program gaining more than 1000 hours of coding experience. Focusing on Web Development using MEAN stack and Python, and iOS development using Swift:

- Interactive BeerPong(1st place CodingDojo Hackathon among 12 teams): Designed and developed an Arduino based embedded system that uses a photosensor to detect when a player have scored a point, and displays the scores on the scoreboard UI. *Technologies*: node.js, express, socket.io, johnny-five, JavaScript, HTML, CSS.
- Events Near Me(1st place CodingDojo Hackathon among 12 teams): Designed and developed an event discovery platform that allows users to discover, rate and review local events. After logging in, user sees a map of events to goto and can express their interest in events they are interested in going to and can also leave a review for others. *Technologies:* Flask, Bootstrap, JS, MySQL, Google API.
- Beauty Product Browser: A web application that allows users to browse the Amazon product catalog related to beauty products. It also uses node-cache module to cache AWS response on server-side reducing the page load time from 1.2s to 300ms. *Technologies:* node.js, express, JavaScript, Angular-JS, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, AWS, Heroku. *Demo:* beauty-product-browser.herokuapp.com

SMC, Pune, India

Web Developer | July 2013 - June 2014

 Designed, developed and maintained company's online presence website. *Technologies*: JavaScript, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, jQuery.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Python, Java, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, Swift Frameworks: node.js, AngularJS, Express, Bootstrap, jQuery, jinja

Technologies: Heroku, AWS S3, AWS Beanstalk, AWS Lambda, MySQL, MongoDB, DynamoDB, git, Bash, github